{"qid": "0", "question": "Can you inform me who are the authors of \"Patient-Specific Physiological Monitoring And Prediction Using Structured Gaussian Processes?\" ", "answer": "Yang Yang, Chris Pugh, Kate Niehaus, Clare MacEwen, Glen W. Colopy, D Clifton, Tingting Zhu"}
{"qid": "1", "question": "Can you inform me who are the authors of \"Long Range Optical Truck Tracking.?\" ", "answer": "Dietrich Paulus, Christian Winkens"}
{"qid": "2", "question": "Can you inform me who are the authors of \"0.33 mm 2 13.3 dB gain sub-6 GHz to 28 GHz transformer-coupled low-voltage upconversion mixer for 5G applications?\" ", "answer": "Oner Hanay, Renato Negra"}
{"qid": "3", "question": "Could you tell me the authors of the paper \"Physical parameter extraction over urban areas using L-band POLSAR data and interferometric baseline diversity?\" ", "answer": "Stefan Sauer, Eric Pottier, Laurent Ferro-Famil, Andreas Reigber"}
{"qid": "4", "question": "Who are the authors of paper \"A New Node Deployment and Location Dispatch Algorithm for Underwater Sensor Networks.?\" ", "answer": "Lurong Jiang, Peng Jiang, Binfeng Ruan, Jun Liu, Feng Wu"}
{"qid": "5", "question": "Who are the authors of paper \"Distributed global development parametric cost modeling?\" ", "answer": "Raymond J. Madachy"}
{"qid": "6", "question": "Could you tell me the authors of the paper \"BlockHammer: Improving Flash Reliability by Exploiting Process Variation Aware Proactive Failure Prediction?\" ", "answer": "Fei Wu, Wenmin Zhong, Qiulin Wu, Changsheng Xie, Zhonghai Lu, Ruixiang Ma, Jiguang Wan"}
{"qid": "7", "question": "Can you tell me who wrote the paper \"Biologically Inspired Neural Controller For Robot Learning And Mapping?\" ", "answer": "Alejandra Barrera Ramirez, Alfredo Weitzenfeld Ridel"}
{"qid": "8", "question": "Can you tell me who wrote the paper \"Sub-Bottom Sediment Classification Using Reliable Instantaneous Frequency Calculation and Relaxation Time Estimation?\" ", "answer": "Hongmei Zhang, Jianhu Zhao, Shaobo Li, Siheng Qu"}
{"qid": "9", "question": "Could you tell me the authors of the paper \"Robust assembly line balancing with heterogeneous workers?\" ", "answer": "Jean-Fran\u00e7ois Cordeau, Gilbert Laporte, Mayron C\u00e9sar O. Moreira, Alysson M. Costa"}
{"qid": "10", "question": "What organization is researcher Justin Booth-Clibborn affiliated with?", "answer": "New York, New York"}
{"qid": "11", "question": "What organization is researcher Greg Daville affiliated with?", "answer": "Hove East Sussex, United Kingdom"}
{"qid": "12", "question": "Which organization does researcher Kohta Morie belong to?", "answer": "Transistor Studio, Japan"}
{"qid": "13", "question": "Can you tell me the affiliation of the researcher Coke Ferreiro?", "answer": "Spain"}
{"qid": "14", "question": "Can you tell me the affiliation of the researcher C. A. Petri?", "answer": "GMD Bonn Germany Germany"}
{"qid": "15", "question": "Can you tell me the affiliation of the researcher Nikita Deshpande?", "answer": "DSK Supinfocom, Pune"}
{"qid": "16", "question": "Which institution is the researcher Franz Von Kutschera associated with?", "answer": "Philosophische Fakult\u00c4t I Universit\u00c4t Regensburg Universit\u00c4tstrasse 31 Postfach 397 8400 Regensburg Germany"}
{"qid": "17", "question": "Can you tell me the affiliation of the researcher Marcin Kobylecki?", "answer": "Warszawa, Poland"}
{"qid": "18", "question": "Which organization does researcher Theo D\u2019Hondt belong to?", "answer": "Vrije Universiteit Brussel Belgium"}
{"qid": "19", "question": "Which institution is the researcher Arthur Lemmens associated with?", "answer": "Amsterdam"}
{"qid": "20", "question": "Where is the paper \"Scalable Lossless And Lossy Image Coding Based On The Rwhat Plus P Pyramid And The Inter-Coefficient Classification Method\" published?", "answer": "2008 IEEE INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON MULTIMEDIA AND EXPO, VOLS 1-4"}
{"qid": "21", "question": "In which place was the paper \"A method for sub-sample computation of time displacements between discrete signals based only on discrete correlation sequences.\" published?", "answer": "Biomedical Signal Processing and Control"}
{"qid": "22", "question": "What is the publication location for the paper \"Private sector needs for trusted/secure computer systems\"?", "answer": "AFIPS National Computer Conference"}
{"qid": "23", "question": "In which place was the paper \"Design Of Ring Oscillator Structures For Measuring Isolated Nbti And Pbti\" published?", "answer": "2012 IEEE INTERNATIONAL SYMPOSIUM ON CIRCUITS AND SYSTEMS (ISCAS 2012)"}
{"qid": "24", "question": "In which place was the paper \"Cooperative Aerial Manipulation with Decentralized Adaptive Force-Consensus Control\" published?", "answer": "Journal of Intelligent & Robotic Systems"}
{"qid": "25", "question": "Where has the paper \"On the evaluation of the Eigenvalues of a banded toeplitz block matrix\" been published?", "answer": "Journal of Complexity"}
{"qid": "26", "question": "Where has the paper \"Lbp Channels For Pedestrian Detection\" been published?", "answer": "2018 IEEE WINTER CONFERENCE ON APPLICATIONS OF COMPUTER VISION (WACV 2018)"}
{"qid": "27", "question": "Where is the paper \"Calculation of Generalized Polynomial-Chaos Basis Functions and Gauss Quadrature Rules in Hierarchical Uncertainty Quantification\" published?", "answer": "Computer-Aided Design of Integrated Circuits and Systems, IEEE Transactions \u00a0"}
{"qid": "28", "question": "Can you tell me the publication venue of the paper \"Effects Of Wind Estimation Errors On Ocean Surface Current Retrieval For A Doppler Scatterometer\"?", "answer": "IGARSS 2020 - 2020 IEEE INTERNATIONAL GEOSCIENCE AND REMOTE SENSING SYMPOSIUM"}
{"qid": "29", "question": "Where is the paper \"High Performance Parallel Optical Flow Algorithms on the Sony Playstation 3\" published?", "answer": "VMV"}
{"qid": "30", "question": "Who teamed up with author Martin Kozek at Vienna Univ Technol, Inst Mech & Mechatron, Div Control & Proc Automat, A-1040 Vienna, Austria to write the paper \"Estimation of molecular weight distribution of CIS-polyisoprene melts from dielectric loss spectra using neural networks\"?", "answer": "Denis Miklau, Jorgl, H.P."}
{"qid": "31", "question": "Who teamed up with author ignatio madanhire at Univ Johannesburg, Dept Qual & Operat Management, Johannesburg, South Africa to write the paper \"Cleaner production as a tool to mitigate pollution in leather processing: Case study\"?", "answer": "Charles Mbohwa"}
{"qid": "32", "question": "Who collaborate with author A. V. Simonova in National Research Tomsk Polytechnic University, Russia to write paper \"The fast neutron irradiation influence on the AlGaAs IR-LEDs reliability.\"?", "answer": "A. V. Gradoboev, K. N. Orlova, I. A. Asanov"}
{"qid": "33", "question": "Who joined forces with author Bao N Nguyen at Univ Leeds, Sch Chem, Inst Proc Res & Dev, Leeds LS2 9JT, W Yorkshire, England to write the research paper \"Predicting Solvent-Dependent Nucleophilicity Parameter with a Causal Structure Property Relationship\"?", "answer": "Samuel Boobier, Yufeng Liu, Krishna Sharma, A. J. Blacker, David R J Hose, Nikil Kapur"}
{"qid": "34", "question": "Who joined forces with author Vijay Varadharajan at University of Western Sydney School of Computing and IT 10 Kingswood NSW 2747 Australia to write the research paper \"A logic for state transformations in authorization policies\"?", "answer": "Yun Bai"}
{"qid": "35", "question": "Who teamed up with author Jos\u00e9 A. Castellanos at Univ Zaragoza, Dept Informat & Ingn Sistemas, C Maria Luna 3, E-50015 Zaragoza, Spain to write the paper \"A fast and accurate approximation for planar pose graph optimization\"?", "answer": "Basilio Bona, Luca Carlone, Rosario Aragues"}
{"qid": "36", "question": "Who teamed up with author Ken Yocum at Department of Computer Science|Duke University to write the paper \"Grid allocation and reservation - Improving grid resource allocation via integrated selection and binding\"?", "answer": "Yang-Suk Kee, Henri Casanova, Andrew A. Chien"}
{"qid": "37", "question": "Who collaborate with author Alexey Stupnikov in Queens Univ Belfast, Computat Biol & Machine Learning Lab, Ctr Canc Res & Cell Biol, Sch Med Dent & Biomed Sci,Fac Med Hlth & Life Sci, Belfast BT9 7AE, Antrim, North Ireland to write paper \"samExploreR: exploring reproducibility and robustness of RNA-seq results based on SAM files.\"?", "answer": "Darragh G. McArt, Ricardo de Matos Simoes, Galina V. Glazko, Shailesh Tripathi, Matthias Dehmer, Frank Emmert-streib, Manuel Salto-Tellez"}
{"qid": "38", "question": "Who worked with Antonio Torralba from Massachusetts Institute of Technology on the paper titled \"Unbiased look at dataset bias\"?", "answer": "Alexei A. Efros"}
{"qid": "39", "question": "Who collaborate with author Zhongxuan Luo in Dalian Univ Technol, Sch Math Sci, Dalian 116621, Peoples R China to write paper \"A High-Capacity 3D Steganography Algorithm With Adjustable Distortion.\"?", "answer": "RiMing Sun, Jiangbei Hu, Nannan Li, Shengfa Wang"}
{"qid": "40", "question": "Who is the author of both \"Trust computation for multiple routes recommendation in social network sites.\" and \"A Sentiment Delivering Estimate Scheme Based on Trust Chain in Mobile Social Network.\" papers?", "answer": "Zhenhua Huang"}
{"qid": "41", "question": "Who writed both the paper \"Performance of Electric Power Systems Under Physical Malicious Attacks.\" and paper \"Critical Infrastructures: The Need For International Risk Governance\"?", "answer": "Wolfgang Kr\u00f6ger"}
{"qid": "42", "question": "Who is the author of both \"Emergent Behavior in Swarms with On-board Sensing.\" and \"Secure robotics.\" papers?", "answer": "Daniel M. Lofaro"}
{"qid": "43", "question": "Who is the author of both \"A design theory for systems that support emergent knowledge processes\" and \"Introduction To The 2004 Ais Award Papers On Innovation In Information Systems Education\" papers?", "answer": "M.Lynne Markus"}
{"qid": "44", "question": "Who penned both \"Reflecting on social influence in networks\" and \"Liquid Democracy: An Analysis in Binary Aggregation and Diffusion.\"?", "answer": "Zo\u00e9 Christoff"}
{"qid": "45", "question": "Who has written both the \"Efficient Hybrid Continuous-Time/Discrete-Time \u2211 \u0394 Modulators for Broadband Wireless Telecom Systems.\" and \"Undersampling RF-to-digital CT \u03a3\u0394 modulator with tunable notch frequency and simplified raised-cosine FIR feedback DAC.\" papers?", "answer": "Jos\u00e9 Manuel de la Rosa"}
{"qid": "46", "question": "Who has written both the \"Multicast communication in wormhole-routed star graph interconnection networks\" and \"Performance of adaptive multistage interference canceller for multi-carrier CDMA systems\" papers?", "answer": "Nen-Chung Wang"}
{"qid": "47", "question": "Who penned both \"Dismantling the Environmental Context - the Role of Environmental Characteristics in the Organizational Adoption of Open Standard-Based Inter-Organizational Information Systems.\" and \"Maternal Identity and Maternal Role Attainment - Determinants of mothers' Participation in Maternal Virtual Communities.\"?", "answer": "Julia Kr\u00f6nung"}
{"qid": "48", "question": "Who writed both the paper \"Model-based coupling approach for non-iterative real-time co-simulation\" and paper \"Discrete Time Sliding Mode Control Strategies For Buffered Networked Systems\"?", "answer": "Martin Horn"}
{"qid": "49", "question": "Who penned both \"Real-time connected-word recognition in a noisy environment\" and \"A 10000-word continuous-speech recognition system\"?", "answer": "h piotrowski"}
{"qid": "50", "question": "Who within Dept. of Electr. & Comput. Eng., Univ. of Rochester, Rochester, NY, USA|c| has the highest number of collaborations with author Renatas Jakushokas?", "answer": "Eby G. Friedman"}
{"qid": "51", "question": "Who is the closest collaborator with author Igor Moreira in Brazilian Telecommun Agcy, Enforcement Superintendency, Brasilia, DF, Brazil? Closeness is defined in terms of the number of collaboration together.", "answer": "Cecilio Pimentel"}
{"qid": "52", "question": "Who is the closest collaborator with author Abhishek Kumar Verma in Univ Calif Merced, Dept Mech Engn, Merced, CA 95343 USA? Closeness is defined in terms of the number of collaboration together.", "answer": "Ayyaswamy Venkattraman"}
{"qid": "53", "question": "Who within HEBREW UNIV JERUSALEM,INST MATH & COMP SCI,IL-9104 JERUSALEM,ISRAEL has the highest number of collaborations with author Shimon Cohen?", "answer": "nathan intrator"}
{"qid": "54", "question": "Who within Northwestern Polytech Univ, Coll Automat, Xian 710129, Shaanxi, Peoples R China has the highest number of collaborations with author Lei Yu?", "answer": "Bingchang Zhou"}
{"qid": "55", "question": "Who is the closest collaborator with author Bruce J. Schachter in Univ. of Maryland, College Park, MD? Closeness is defined in terms of the number of collaboration together.", "answer": "Azriel Rosenfeld"}
{"qid": "56", "question": "Who is the closest collaborator with author Chenhao Pei in Fuzhou Univ, Coll Phys & Informat Engn, Fuzhou, Peoples R China? Closeness is defined in terms of the number of collaboration together.", "answer": "Liqin Huang"}
{"qid": "57", "question": "Who within Tufts Univ, Medford, MA 02155 USA has the highest number of collaborations with author Fumeng Yang?", "answer": "Steven Franconeri"}
{"qid": "58", "question": "Who is the closest collaborator with author Rubem Toledo Bergamo in Dept. of Telecommun. Eng., Fed. Inst. of Educ., Florianopolis, Brazil|c|? Closeness is defined in terms of the number of collaboration together.", "answer": "Paulo Cardieri"}
{"qid": "59", "question": "Who within Instituto Polit\u00e9cnico Nacional, ESIME Azcapotzalco, Secci\u00f3n de Estudios de Posgrado e Investigaci\u00f3n, Av. de las Granjas no.682, Col. Santa Catarina, Delegaci\u00f3n Azcapotz ... has the highest number of collaborations with author Jaime Pacheco?", "answer": "Jos\u00e9 De Jes\u00fas Rubio"}
{"qid": "60", "question": "How many collaborators does author Christian Koidl in Salzburg Univ, Dept Comp Sci, A-5020 Salzburg, Austria have in 2011", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "61", "question": "What is the number of people that Ekkapong Promin from Management of Information Technology collaborated with in 2019", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "62", "question": "How many collaborators does author Songyan Yang in School of Biological Science and Medical Engineering, Beihang University, Beijing, China have in 2011", "answer": "7"}
{"qid": "63", "question": "Can you tell me the number of collaborators of author Yi Chen from Beihang Univ, State Key Lab Virtual Real Technol & Syst, Sch Comp Sci & Engn, Beijing, Peoples R China in the year 2013", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "64", "question": "Can you tell me the number of collaborators of author Xu Wu from Department of Computer Science, Xi'an Institute of Posts and Telecommunications, Xi'an, China in the year 2012", "answer": "0"}
{"qid": "65", "question": "Can you tell me the number of collaborators of author Alexei D. Sadovnikov from Dept. of Electr. & Comput. Eng., Waterloo Univ., Ont., Canada|c| in the year 1993", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "66", "question": "Can you tell me the number of collaborators of author Hyeyun Jeong from Department of Electrical Engineering, Pohang University of Science and Technology, Pohang, South Korea in the year 2021", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "67", "question": "In the year 1985, how many people collaborated with author Charles Bigelow at Stanford University", "answer": "10"}
{"qid": "68", "question": "In the year 2018, how many people collaborated with author Byunghee Moon at Inha Univ, Elect Engn Dept, Incheon 22212, South Korea", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "69", "question": "What is the number of people that A. Yonezawa from Graduate Sch. of Inf. Sci. & Technol., Tokyo Univ., Japan collaborated with in 2005", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "70", "question": "What is the number of papers that David Martin from CICtourGUNE, Asociac Ctr Invest Cooperat Turismo, Mikeletegi Pasealekua 56, Donostia San Sebastian, Spain and Emilio Torres-Manzanera from Univ Oviedo, Dept Stat, Gijon 33003, Spain co-authored?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "71", "question": "Do you know the number of collective papers Anran Yang at Natl Univ Def Technol, Coll Elect Sci & Engn, Changsha 410073, Hunan, Peoples R China and Ning Jing at Natl Univ Def Technol, Coll Elect Sci & Engn, Changsha 410073, Hunan, Peoples R China have produced?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "72", "question": "Can you tell me the count of papers written jointly by Asmaa Halbouni at Int Islamic Univ Malaysia, Dept Elect & Comp Engn, Kuala Lumpur 53100, Malaysia and Murad Halbouni at Arab Amer Univ, Dept Nat Engn & Technol Sci, Jenin 240, Palestine?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "73", "question": "Can you tell me the count of papers written jointly by Kamini Sabu at Department of Electrical Engineering, Indian Institute of Technology Bombay, India and Rao, Preeti at Indian Inst Technol, Dept Elect Engn, Mumbai 400076, Maharashtra, India?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "74", "question": "Do you know the number of collective papers Gerben S. Van der Vegt at Department of Human Resource Management and Organizational Behavior, University of Groningen, 9700 AV Groningen, The Netherlands and J. Stuart Bunderson at John M. Olin School of Business, Washington University in St. Louis, St. Louis, Missouri 63130 have produced?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "75", "question": "What is the number of papers that Lance A. Miller from IBM Watson Research Center, Yorktown Heights, NY and Karen Jensen from IBM Thomas J. Watson Research Center, Yorktown Heights, NY co-authored?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "76", "question": "What is the number of papers that Michael Trcka from vienna university of economics and business and Martin Natter from Department of Industrial Information Processing, University of Economics, A-1200 Vienna, Austria co-authored?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "77", "question": "Do you know the number of collective papers Lukas Graf at Augsburg Univ, Inst Math, Augsburg, Germany and Tobias Harks at Univ Augsburg, Inst Math, D-86135 Augsburg, Germany have produced?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "78", "question": "Can you tell me the count of papers written jointly by B. Y. Qu at Nanyang Technological University, School of Electrical and Electronics Engineering, Singapore and Yongsheng Zhu at Theory of Lubrication and Bearing Institute, Xi\u2019an Jiaotong University, Xi\u2019an, China 710049?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "79", "question": "What is the number of papers that Jinwang Zheng from Southeast University, Nanjing, China and Weiwei Ni from Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Southeast University, Nanjing 210096, PR China co-authored?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "80", "question": "How many academic works referenced the paper \"Model of experts for decision support in the diagnosis of leukemia patients\"?", "answer": "31"}
{"qid": "81", "question": "Can you tell me the count of papers that cite \"Automated Aspect Recommendation through Clustering-Based Fan-in Analysis\"?", "answer": "12"}
{"qid": "82", "question": "Can you tell me the count of papers that cite \"Parsimonious translation models for information retrieval\"?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "83", "question": "Can you tell me the count of papers that cite \"A View from the Bottom: Nanometer Technology AC Parametric Failures \" Why, Where, and How to Detect\"?", "answer": "10"}
{"qid": "84", "question": "How many academic works referenced the paper \"Cryptology and Network Security, 7th International Conference, CANS 2008, Hong-Kong, China, December 2-4, 2008. Proceedings\"?", "answer": "22"}
{"qid": "85", "question": "How many papers cite the paper \"Topology-aware reliability optimization for multiprocessor systems\"?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "86", "question": "What is the number of publications that cite the paper \"Optimal Kinodynamic Motion Planning for 2D Reconfiguration of Self-Reconfigurable Robots\"?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "87", "question": "How many papers cite the paper \"The DVB multimedia home platform (MHP) and related specifications\"?", "answer": "16"}
{"qid": "88", "question": "How many papers cite the paper \"A Scoping Review Of Transfer Learning Research On Medical Image Analysis Using Imagenet\"?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "89", "question": "How many papers cite the paper \"Linear colour contouring for fine art printmaking\"?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "90", "question": "What is the number of papers cited by the paper \"Generation, testing and recommendation of teaching materials using classification learning\"?", "answer": "7"}
{"qid": "91", "question": "How many citations does the paper \"Geometric Detection Of Chaos By Using A Delayed Lorenz Map\" have?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "92", "question": "How many citations does the paper \"An OPS5 implementation of qualitative reasoning about physical systems\" have?", "answer": "7"}
{"qid": "93", "question": "What is the number of papers cited by the paper \"The roofline model for oceanic climate applications\"?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "94", "question": "What is the number of papers cited by the paper \"Optimal Free Binary Decision Diagrams for Computation of EARn\"?", "answer": "7"}
{"qid": "95", "question": "How many papers does paper \"Efficient Affine 2D-image Registration Using Evolutionary Strategies\" cite?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "96", "question": "How many papers does paper \"Chinese OOV translation and post-translation query expansion in chinese--english cross-lingual information retrieval\" cite?", "answer": "25"}
{"qid": "97", "question": "How many papers does paper \"Multi-objective multi-population biased random-key genetic algorithm for the 3-D container loading problem\" cite?", "answer": "19"}
{"qid": "98", "question": "What is the number of papers cited by the paper \"Simulation optimization applied to injection molding\"?", "answer": "9"}
{"qid": "99", "question": "How many papers does paper \"Ball packings with high chromatic numbers from strongly regular graphs\" cite?", "answer": "8"}
{"qid": "100", "question": "Can you tell me the most referenced paper of J. A. Jensen from Electron. Inst., Tech. Univ. of Denmark, Lyngby, Denmark|c|?", "answer": "Stationary echo canceling in velocity estimation by time-domain cross-correlation."}
{"qid": "101", "question": "What is the most frequently cited paper written by Bouveret Geraldine at Nanyang Technological University?", "answer": "A Level-Set Approach for Stochastic Optimal Control Problems Under Controlled-Loss Constraints"}
{"qid": "102", "question": "Which is the most cited paper by author Kun Yu in School of information Engineering, Chang'an University,Xi'an,Shaanxi Province,P. R. China?", "answer": "Person Movement and Stay Classification Based on Base Station Network Data."}
{"qid": "103", "question": "Can you tell me the most referenced paper of Xieting Ling from Fudan University(Fudan University),Shanghai,China?", "answer": "Minor component analysis with implementation to blind 2-channel equalization"}
{"qid": "104", "question": "The most quoted paper of Atsuhiko Maeda in NTT Corp, Network Innovat Labs, 3-9-11 Midori Cho, Musashino, Tokyo 1808585, Japan is what?", "answer": "Mobile walking game and group-walking program to enhance going out for older adults."}
{"qid": "105", "question": "What is the most frequently cited paper written by Kazemi, M.H. at Dept. of Electr. Eng., Amir Kabir Univ., Tehran, Iran|c|?", "answer": "Multivariable adaptive output-feedback control"}
{"qid": "106", "question": "Can you tell me the most referenced paper of Diego Guar\u00edn from Dept. of Electr. Eng., Univ. Tecnol. de Pereira, Pereira, Colombia|c|?", "answer": "Testing for nonlinearity in non-stationary physiological time series."}
{"qid": "107", "question": "What is the most frequently cited paper written by Carlos Ivan Briones-Herrera at Univ Juarez Estado Durango, Fac Ciencias Forestales, Rio Papaloapan Blvd,Durango S-N Col Valle Sur, Durango 34120, Mexico?", "answer": "Near Real-Time Automated Early Mapping of the Perimeter of Large Forest Fires from the Aggregation of VIIRS and MODIS Active Fires in Mexico."}
{"qid": "108", "question": "What is the most frequently cited paper written by Amanda Minter at Harvard TH Chan Sch Publ Hlth, Ctr Communicable Dis Dynam, Dept Epidemiol, Boston, MA 02115 USA?", "answer": "An open source tool to infer epidemiological and immunological dynamics from serological data: Serosolver."}
{"qid": "109", "question": "The most quoted paper of Anna Bogacka in School of English & Center for Speech and Language Processing|Adam Mickiewicz University is what?", "answer": "General and Task-Specific Corpus Resources for Polish Adult Learners of English"}
{"qid": "110", "question": "Can you tell me how many papers were written by Nicolai Meinshausen from Department of Statistics, UC Berkeley, 367 Evans Hall, Berkeley, CA 94720-3860, USA?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "111", "question": "What number of papers has Andrej Gabris at Brno Univ Technol, Cent European Inst Technol, Brno 61200, Czech Republic authored?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "112", "question": "Can you tell me how many papers were written by Jingjing Liu from Education Faculty Beijing Normal University, CHN?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "113", "question": "What is the number of papers Caroline D Monteiro wrote at Department of Pharmacology and Systems Therapeutics, Icahn School of Medicine at Mount Sinai, New York, NY 10029, USA, BD2K-LINCS Data Coordination and Integration Center, Mount Sinai Knowledge Management Center for Illuminating the Druggable Genome and 367 Airport Sector, Goiania, Goias 74075, Brazil.?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "114", "question": "What number of papers has Lubos Gaspar at Hubert Curien Laboratory, Jean Monnet University authored?", "answer": "8"}
{"qid": "115", "question": "What is the number of papers Sebastien Lasserre wrote at Technicolor, Cesson-S\u00e9vign\u00e9 Cedex, France?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "116", "question": "How many papers did author rui he in anhui university write?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "117", "question": "What number of papers has Gullelala Jadoon at Univ Haripur, Dept Informat Technol, Haripur, Pakistan authored?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "118", "question": "How many papers did author Chris Sharman in CSIRO, Tasmanian ICT Ctr, Hobart, Tas 7000, Australia write?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "119", "question": "What is the number of papers Aimee Rickman wrote at University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, Urbana, IL, US?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "120", "question": "Which venue did S. L. Guo in Southeast Univ, Int Inst Urban Syst Engn, Nanjing, Jiangsu, Peoples R China and Q. Q. Zhang in Southeast Univ, Int Inst Urban Syst Engn, Nanjing, Jiangsu, Peoples R China collaborate most?", "answer": "COMPUTER-AIDED CIVIL AND INFRASTRUCTURE ENGINEERING"}
{"qid": "121", "question": "Where did most of the collaboration between Yang Cui in Harbin Inst Technol, Commun Res Ctr, Harbin, Heilongjiang, Peoples R China and Boyang An in Harbin Inst Technol Weihai, Off Retirement Serv, Weihai 264209, Peoples R China occur?", "answer": "IEEE ACCESS"}
{"qid": "122", "question": "Where did most of the collaboration between Rui Huang in Institute of Automation, Bohai University, Jinzhou, China and Huanqing Wang in Department of Mathematics, Bohai University, Jinzhou, China occur?", "answer": "IEEE Transactions on Circuits and Systems II: Express Briefs"}
{"qid": "123", "question": "What is the venue where most collaborations between Ning Cao from Artificial Intelligence Acad, Wuxi Vocat Coll Sci & Technol, Wuxi 214068, Jiangsu, Peoples R China and Leilei Li from Artificial Intelligence Acad, Wuxi Vocat Coll Sci & Technol, Wuxi 214068, Jiangsu, Peoples R China took place?", "answer": "JOURNAL OF HIGH SPEED NETWORKS"}
{"qid": "124", "question": "Where did most of the collaboration between Hongyu Lin in Tongji Zhejiang Coll, Dept Elect & Informat Engn, Jiaxing 314051, Peoples R China and Zhiyong Chen in Tongji Zhejiang Coll, Dept Phys Educ, Jiaxing 314051, Peoples R China occur?", "answer": "IEEE ACCESS"}
{"qid": "125", "question": "Which venue did Douglas W. Ball in JOHNS HOPKINS UNIV,SCH MED,DEPT MED,424 N BOND ST,BALTIMORE,MD 21231, USA and Andr\u00e9e de Bustros in JOHNS HOPKINS UNIV,SCH MED,CTR ONCOL,BALTIMORE,MD 21231 collaborate most?", "answer": "NUCLEIC ACIDS RESEARCH"}
{"qid": "126", "question": "Which venue did J. Jenny Li in UNIV WATERLOO,BELL CANADA SOFTWARE RELIABIL LAB,WATERLOO,ON N2L 3G1,CANADA and D. A. Simser in UNIV WATERLOO,BELL CANADA SOFTWARE RELIABIL LAB,WATERLOO,ON N2L 3G1,CANADA collaborate most?", "answer": "SIXTH INTERNATIONAL SYMPOSIUM ON SOFTWARE RELIABILITY ENGINEERING, PROCEEDINGS"}
{"qid": "127", "question": "What is the venue where most collaborations between An\u0111ela Blagojevi\u0107 from Faculty of Engineering, University of Kragujevac, Kragujevac, Serbia and Tijana Sustersic from Faculty of Engineering, University of Kragujevac, Kragujevac, Serbia took place?", "answer": "2021 IEEE 21st International Conference on Bioinformatics and Bioengineering (BIBE)"}
{"qid": "128", "question": "Where did most of the collaboration between Xiong Wang in Northwestern Polytech Univ, Sch Comp Sci, Xian, Shaanxi, Peoples R China and Weipeng He in TAMS group, Department of Informatiks, University of Hamburg, Vogt-Koelln-Strasse 30 occur?", "answer": "2021 IEEE SPOKEN LANGUAGE TECHNOLOGY WORKSHOP (SLT)"}
{"qid": "129", "question": "Where did most of the collaboration between Shuang Li in Ohio State Univ, Dept CSE, Columbus, OH 43210 USA and Eylem Ekici in Ohio State Univ, Dept Elect & Comp Engn, Columbus, OH 43210 USA occur?", "answer": "IEEE Trans. Mob. Comput."}
{"qid": "130", "question": "What is the least count of people whom Omar, H.M. at Qassim Uinvers, Dept Mech Engn, Burriydah, Saudi Arabia should know to get introduced to Mohamed Slim Masmoudi at Ecole Natl Ingenieurs Sfax, Elect Engn Dept, BP W, Sfax 3038, Tunisia?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "131", "question": "To be familiar with Paul Gastin of LSV, ENS Paris-Saclay & CNRS, Universit\u00e9 Paris-Saclay, France, how many people at minimum should Shankara Narayanan Krishna from Dept of CSE, IIT Bombay, India know?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "132", "question": "To be familiar with Qingsheng Ren of Shanghai Jiao Tong Univ, Dept Comp Sci & Engn, Shanghai 200240, Peoples R China, how many people at minimum should Fariba Islam from Department of Electrical and Electronic Engineering, Bangladesh University of Engineering and Technology, Dhaka know?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "133", "question": "How many people, at the very least, should B. Morgenfeld from IBM Microelect, Hopewell Jct, NY 12533 USA be acquainted with to know T. J. McArdle in IBM Microelect, Hopewell Jct, NY 12533 USA?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "134", "question": "How many people, at the very least, should Maria Carla Piastra from Cognitive Neuroscience, Donders Institute for Brain, Cognition and Behaviour, Radboud University Nijmegen Medical Centre, Kapittelweg 29, Nijmegen 6525 EN, the Netherlands be acquainted with to know Atena Rezaei in Corresponding author.?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "135", "question": "To be familiar with Amzad Hussain Tamim of Leading University, how many people at minimum should Md Rumman Hussain Khan Rahib from Leading University know?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "136", "question": "To be familiar with M. R. Asim of Univ Engn & Technol, Dept Comp Sci & Engn, Lahore, Pakistan, how many people at minimum should Grayson Silaski from GRAYSON SILASKI , Portland, USA know?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "137", "question": "What is the least count of people whom P. Sorotou at Univ Athens, Dept Geol & Geoenvironm, Panepistimioupoli Zografou, Athens 15784, Greece should know to get introduced to e n zois at Electronics Laboratory, Physics Department, University of Patras, Patras 26500, Greece?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "138", "question": "What is the least count of people whom Chaoliang Zhang at Key Laboratory of Universal Wireless Communication, Ministry of Education, Beijing University of Posts and Telecommunications, Beijing, 100876, China should know to get introduced to Yaohua Sun at Beijing Univ Posts & Telecommun, State Key Lab Networking & Switching Technol, Beijing 100876, Peoples R China?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "139", "question": "To be familiar with Roland Olsson of Ostfold Univ Coll, Halden, Norway, how many people at minimum should Huyen Vu from Ostfold Univ Coll, Halden, Norway know?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "140", "question": "What are the top three areas of research interest for Wenyong He at Central South University?", "answer": "Adversarial examples,  Graph convolutional network,  Graph theory metrics"}
{"qid": "141", "question": "What is the research interests (top 3 keywords) of author Timothy M. Platt in Clarkson University, Potsdam, NY, USA?", "answer": "FPGA accelerators, OpenCL, test time reduction"}
{"qid": "142", "question": "What are the top three areas of research interest for Hiroyuki Sato at Tokyo Institute of Technology|Software Research Associates , Inc?", "answer": "data replication, system design, data management"}
{"qid": "143", "question": "Can you tell me the top 3 research interest keywords of the author Yanxin Zhao from Tongji Univ, Shanghai Peoples Hosp 10, Sch Med, Shanghai, Peoples R China?", "answer": "text mining, ABC model, stroke"}
{"qid": "144", "question": "What is the research interests (top 3 keywords) of author Roy L. Simpson in Emory Univ, Atlanta, GA 30322 USA?", "answer": "Sequential pattern mining,  Healthcare data"}
{"qid": "145", "question": "Could you share the primary research interests, in the form of three keywords, of the author Anil Armagan in Institute of Computer Graphics, Vision Graz University of Technology, Austria?", "answer": "semantic segmentation, urban environments, 3D localization"}
{"qid": "146", "question": "What is the research interests (top 3 keywords) of author Yonas T. Weldeselassie in Simon Fraser Univ, Med Image Anal Lab, Sch Comp Sci, Burnaby, BC V5A 1S6, Canada?", "answer": "diffusion tensor magnetic resonance imaging, J-divergence, Segmentation"}
{"qid": "147", "question": "What are the top three areas of research interest for Letian Qi at Southwest Univ, Coll Elect & Informat Engn, Chongqing Key Lab Nonlinear Circuits & Intelligen, Chongqing 400715, Peoples R China?", "answer": "Kernel,  Noise measurement,  Loss measurement"}
{"qid": "148", "question": "Can you tell me the top 3 research interest keywords of the author Derek Huynh from Texas Instruments?", "answer": "dual-core architecture, dedicated functional block, low power"}
{"qid": "149", "question": "What is the research interests (top 3 keywords) of author Wenpeng Xing in Hong Kong Baptist University?", "answer": "Multi-plane image, Neural basis learning, Novel view synthesis"}
